iplocation.net 2015-12-25

# Privacy Policy

## 1\. PRIVACY STATEMENT

IP Location respects your privacy and is comitted to protecting your privacy. Personally identifiable information about you is not willfully discolsed to any third party without your consent. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting any of the sites offered by IP Location, an Edula company, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

## 2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION

IP Location collects personal information such as name, address and phone number to provide our services to you. We use your personal information to operate our business, and to deliver services you request. We also use your personal information to inform you of service status as well as products and services available from IP Location.

IP Location does not sell, rent or lease its customer information to third parties. IP Location may access or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, however.

## 3\. COOKIES

IP Location uses "cookies" to improve the quality of our service and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies on your web browser. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use some of our services and features.

## 4\. MINORS

The protection of children's online privacy is very important to us. IP Location does not sell services for purchase by children. If you are under 13, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

## 5\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

IP Location may occasionally update this "Privacy Policy" to better meet our business needs. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of IP Location web site and its services will indicate that you agree with such changes. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we protect your privacy information.

## 6\. QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at admin@iplocation.net.
